article-london.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy — Article.

**GDPR COMPLIANCE**

The Article team members are customers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the internet. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. Therefore, we are totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers.

According to law, we must ask you to agree to handle your personal details. All details that you leave with us, or which we are given when you register for a purchase or visit our homepage will only be used by Article in order to fulfill our undertakings and informing you of offers that will appeal to you. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is a necessary part of providing a service to you - e.g. Arranging for a product to be sent to you. By visiting Article, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "Article") uses and protects any information that you give Article while using this website. Article is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Article may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

 **WHAT WE COLLECT**  
We may collect information such as name, contact information including email address, demographic information such as post code and preferences along with other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.

**DO WE STORE CARD DATA?**

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

**DO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE RECIVE?**

We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and order.

**WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for internal record keeping. We may use the information to improve our products and services and periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

 **SECURITY**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **HOW WE USE COOKIES**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

 **LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.

**E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS**

To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than order notifications and receipts, please adjust your "Subscription" preferences by unsubscribing to the emails.

******CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS******

If you choose to visit Article, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of our local state. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the & "Contact Us" link on the side menu, and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

**QUESTIONS**

Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link in the side menu.

We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and order.
